Guide to the Old Fashioned Revival Hour Collection ARS.0026
Archive of Recorded Sound
Old Fashioned Revival Hour Collection
2007-2010
ARS.0026
Fuller, Charles Edward, 1887-1968
1 box: 127 sound discs (123 CD-Rs; 4 CD-audio); 2 audiocassettes
Archive of Recorded Sound
Evangelical sermons, prayers, and hymnal recordings on Compact Disc, originally broadcast from 1937 to 1968 on the radio program Old Fashioned Revival Hour.
Access
Open for research; material must be requested at least two business days in advance of intended use. Contact the Archive for assistance.
Biographical/Historical note
Charles Fuller (1887-1968) was a Baptist minister and radio evangelist. He gained renown as the radio host and speaker of The Old Fashioned Revival Hour, a weekly Sunday broadcast that aired from 1937 to 1968. The first nationwide broadcast occurred on October 3, 1937, on the Mutual Broadcasting System. Beginning in 1951, the program was carried on the ABC Radio Network, heard on more than 650 radio stations. The Old Fashioned Revival Hour broadcast was originally recorded in a Hollywood studio. In 1941, it was moved to the old Municipal Auditorium in Long Beach, California. From 1941 through 1958, audiences attended services that were broadcast live on the radio from the Long Beach Municipal Auditorium. After January 12, 1958, the program was again produced in a studio, until it ended in 1968. The broadcasts were also noted for the music, featuring the Old Fashioned Revival Hour Choir and quartet, accompanied by organist George Broadbent and pianist Rudy Atwood. Several popular recordings were made by the choir in the 1940s and 1950s. Re-broadcasts of the Old Fashioned Revival Hour are now streamed weekly on the internet.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of Compact Disc copies of radio broadcasts of the Old Fashioned Revival Hour, a program of hymns, prayers, and sermons led by Charles E. Fuller and his wife, plus CDs and cassettes of music. The programs were originally broadcast from approximately 1937 until 1968 and have been re-broadcast on several radio stations since 2002. The collection includes original programs from the 1950s and rebroadcasts from 2002 to the present. More programs will be added as they become available. The music CDs and cassettes were were produced on the campus of Fuller Theological Seminary and were published between 1999 and 2004.
Broadcast information
The radio program originally broadcast from 1937 to 1968. Known original broadcast dates of items in this collection are from Dec. 19, 1954 to Jul. 10, 1955. Rebroadcast from Oct. 7, 2007 to the present.
Indexing Terms
Evangelistic sermons--United States; Gospel music; Hymns, English; Radio sermons
- Radio programs, 1; 123 CD-Rs (Audio 1)
  - Original broadcasts, 1; 3 CD-Rs
    - Program no. 162, Seven marvels of mercy, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 1)
      Original broadcast date
      Jan. 12, 1958
      Historical note
      "Last broadcast from Municipal Auditorium in Long Beach, CA."
    - Program no. 917, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 2)
      Apr. 24, 1955
      Contents
      If your heart keeps right -- He is so precious to me -- Heavenly sunshine -- Medley: He is altogether lovely to me/I've a longing in my heart/Rock of ages hide thou me/Blessed be the name of Jesus/Every moment, every hour/My Lord knows the way throught the wilderness -- Climbin' up the mountain -- Letters -- The love of God -- No not one -- Prayer/invitation -- Send the light -- Bringing in the sheaves -- Nothing between -- Scripture text: Genesis 6 -- Message: The days of Noah -- Invitation hymn: Almost persuaded.
    - Program no. 922.1, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 3)
      May 29, 1955
      We're marching to Zion -- Jesus, what a friend of sinners -- Heavenly sunshine -- Living for Jesus -- There is glory in my soul -- Letters -- Beneath the cross of Jesus -- What a friend we have in Jesus -- Prayer -- Wonderful story of love -- I cannot get beyond his love -- This world is not my home -- Scripture text: Genesis 12 -- Message: The beginning of Israel -- Invitation hymn: Almost persuaded.
  - Rebroadcasts, 2007-2009; 2; 107 CD-Rs
    - Program no. 02-003 and 02-004, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 4)
      Unknown
      Rebroadcast date
      2002
    - Program no. 02-033 and 02-034, My redeemer liveth. Part 1 and 2, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 5)
      Series title
      Job series; no. 2 and 3
    - Program no. 06-52-236, CEF and Christmas music, LK 2:1-20, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 6)
      Dec. 25, 1955
      Dec. 24, 2006
    - Program no. 07-08-244, 1st opposition to the Gospel, Acts 4:1-4, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 7)
      Feb. 2, 1953
      Feb. 25, 2007
    - Program no. 07-11-248, Stephen, the 1st martyr, Acts 6 and 7, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 8)
      Mar. 15, 1953
      Mar. 18, 2007
    - Program no. 07-17-253, Paul's consecration for service, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 9)
      Apr. 12, 1953
      Apr. 22, 2007
    - Program no. 07-18-254, Paul's early training on the backside of the desert, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 10)
      Apr. 10, 1953
      Apr. 29, 2007
    - Program no. 07-19-255, Peter's ministry, Acts 9:22-43, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 11)
      Apr. 26, 1953
      May 6, 2007
    - Program no. 07-20-256, The gospel to the Gentiles, Acts 10:1-23, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 12)
      May 3, 1953
      May 13, 2007
    - Program no. 07-30-266, Spiritual guidance, Acts 15:36, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 13)
      Jul. 19, 1953
      Ju. 22, 2007
    - Program no. 07-35-271, Paul at Berea, Acts 17:16-17, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 14)
      Aug. 23, 1953
      Aug. 26, 2007
    - Program no. 07-36-272, Paul in Athens, Acts 17:16-17, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 15)
      Aug. 30, 1953
      Sept. 2, 2007
    - Program no. 07-37-273, Paul at Corinth, Acts 18:1-22, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 16)
      Sept. 13, 1953
      Sept. 9, 2007
    - Program no. 07-40-276, Paul's discourse to the Ephesian elders, Acts 20:28, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 17)
      Nov. 22, 1953
      Sept. 30, 2007
    - Program no. 07-41-277, Job's longing for an umpire, Job 9:32-33, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 18)
      Mar. 28, 1954
      Oct. 7, 2007
    - Program no. 07-51-287, The robe of righteousness, Ex 25:22, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 19)
      June 13, 1954
      Dec. 16, 2007
    - Program no. 08-01-290, The brazen altar, Ex 27:1-8, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 20)
      June 27, 1954
      Jan. 6, 2008
    - Program no. 08-05-294, The golden altar of incense, Ex 30:1-10, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 21)
      Jul. 25, 1954
      Feb. 23, 2008
    - Program no. 08-06-295, The veil of the tabernacle, Ex 26:31, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 22)
      Aug. 1, 1954
      Feb. 10, 2008
    - Program no. 08-07-296, The ark of the covenant, Ex 25:10-22, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 23)
      Aug. 8, 1954
      Feb. 17, 2008
    - Program no. 08-09-298, The golden pot of manna and Aaron's rod, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 24)
      Alternate title
      The golden altar of incense, Ex 30:1-10 (incorrect)
      Aug. 22, 1954
      Mar. 2, 2008
    - Program no. 08-10-299, The blood sprinkled mercy seat, Ex. 25:17-22, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 25)
      Aug. 20, 1954
      Mar. 9, 2008
    - Program no. 08-11-300, The great day of atonement, Lv 16 and 17, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 26)
      Sept. 5, 1954
      Mar. 16, 2008
    - Program no. 08-13-302, Pillar of cloud and pillar of fire, Ex 13:17-22, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 27)
      Sept. 12, 1954
      Mar. 30, 2008
    - Program no. 08-15-304, Believers when they die, 1 Thes. 4:13, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 28)
      Oct. 24, 1954
      Apr. 13, 2008
    - Program no. 08-16-305, Sorrow-- no hope, 1 Thes. 4:13, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 29)
      Oct. 31, 1954
      Apr. 20, 2008
    - Program no. 08-17-306, Hope of the first resurrection, 1 Thes. 4:13, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 30)
      Nov. 7, 1954
      Apr. 27, 2008
    - Program no. 08-18-307, Is the church the storehouse?, Mal 3:7-11, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 31)
      Nov. 14, 1954
      May 4, 2008
    - Program no. 08-19-308, The blessed hope-- its foundation, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 32)
      Nov. 21, 1954
      May 11, 2008
    - Program no. 08-20-309, The 5 'R's of the Lord's retun, 1 Thes 4:15-18, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 33)
      Nov. 28, 1954
      May 18, 2008
    - Program no. 08-21-310, The believers-- children of light, 1 Thes 4:15-18, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 34)
      Dec. 12, 1954
      May 25, 2008
    - Program no. 08-22-311, Tribulation, 2 Thes 2, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 35)
      Dec. 19, 1954
      June 1, 2008
    - Program no. 08-23-312, The great apostasy, 2 Thes 2, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 36)
      Dec. 26, 1954
      June, 8, 2008
    - Program no. 08-24-313, The day of apostasy, 2 Thes 2, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 37)
      Jan. 2, 1955
      June, 15, 2008
    - Program no. 08-26-315, In the beginning God created, Genesis 1:1, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 38)
      Jan. 16, 1955
      June 29, 2008
    - Program no. 08-27-316, God's loving heart first revealed, Genesis 1:2, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 39)
      Jan. 30, 1955
      Jul. 6, 2008
    - Program no. 08-28-317, God's great object lesson for redemption, Genesis 1:1-3, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 40)
      Feb. 6, 1955
      Jul. 13, 2008
    - Program no. 08-29-318, The two trees, Genesis 2:8, 9, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 41)
      Feb. 13, 1955
      Jul. 20, 2008
    - Program no. 08-30-319, The serpent of Genesis three, Genesis 3, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 42)
      Feb. 20, 1955
      Jul. 27, 2008
    - Program no. 08-31-320, Satan, Devil, Serpent, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 43)
      Feb. 27, 1955
      Aug. 3, 2008
    - Program no. 08-32-321, Where art Thou, Genesis 3:9, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 44)
      Mar. 13, 1955
      Aug. 10, 2008
    - Program no. 08-33-322, The first gospel sermon, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 45)
      Mar. 20, 1955
      Aug. 17, 2008
    - Program no. 08-34-323, Cast out of the garden, Genesis 3:24, 1 compact disc (Audio 1, Disc 46)
      Mar. 27, 1955
      Aug. 24, 2008
    - Program no. 08-35-324, The line of Seth, Genesis 5:21, 22, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 47)
      Apr. 10, 1955
      Aug. 31, 2008
    - Program no. 08-36-326 [?], Noah and the flood, Gen. 8:8-9, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 48)
      Sept. 14, 2008
    - Program no. 08-37-327 [?], Noah: the ark and the flood, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 49)
      May 8, 1955
      Sept. 21, 2008
    - Program no. 08-38-328 [?], The universal destructive force, Gen. 7 and 8, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 50)
      Sept. 28, 2008
    - Program no. 08-39-330 [?], Contrary winds, Mk 6:46, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 51)
      June 5, 1955
      Oct. 12, 2008
    - Program no. 08-40-331 [?], Evangelization of the world in this generation, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 52)
      Oct. 19, 2008
    - Program no. 08-41-332 [?], The hem of his garment, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 53)
      June 19, 1955
      Oct. 26, 2008
    - Program no. 08-42-333 [?], The healing of the blind man, 1 compact disc (Audio 1, Disc 54)
      June 26, 1955
      Nov. 2, 2008
    - Program no. 08-43-334 [?], The cross--Satan bound, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 55)
      Jul. 3, 1955
      Nov. 9, 2008
    - Program no. 08-44-335 [?], Storehouse tithing, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 56)
      Jul. 10, 1955
      Nov. 16, 2008
    - Program no. 08-45-336 [?], Xtian giving: the more excellent way, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 57)
      Nov. 16, 2008 [more likely Nov. 21]
    - Program no. 08-46-337 [?], The Gaderene demoniac, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 58)
      Jul, 31, 1955
      Nov. 30, 2008
    - Program no. 08-47-338 [?], The Lord's coming--Satan bound, Rev: 20 1-3, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 59)
      Aug. 7, 1955
      Dec. 7, 2008
    - Program no. 08-48-339 [?], Satan and the lake of fire, Rev: 20, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 60)
      Aug. 14, 1955
      Dec. 21, 2008 [possibly Dec. 7?]
    - Program no. 08-49-340 [?], CEF and Xmas music, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 61)
      Broadcast date
      Dec. 25, 1955 [same broadcast as CD 236]
      Dec. 21, 2008
    - Program no. 08-50-341 [?], Highlights of Peter's life, 1 Peter 1:1, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 62)
      Aug. 21, 1955
      Dec. 28, 2008
    - Program no. 09-1-342, Strangers scattered, 1 Peter 1:1, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 63)
      Jan. 4, 2009
    - Program no. 09-2-343, God's seed sowers, 1 Peter 1:4, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 64)
      Sept. 4, 1955
      Jan. 11, 2009
    - Program no. 09-3-344, Manifold testing and trials, Peter 1:6-7, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 65)
      Sept. 11, 1955
      Jan. 18, 2009
    - Program no. 09-4-345, The suffering and glory of Christ, 1 Peter 1:10-12, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 66)
      Sept. 18, 1955
      Jan. 25, 2009
    - Program no. 09-5-346, Children of obedience, 1 Peter 1:13-17, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 67)
      February 1, 2009
      September 25, 1955
    - Program no. 09-6-347, Redeemed by blood, 1 Peter 1:18-21, 1 compact disc (Audio 1, Disc 68)
      October 2, 1955
      February 8, 2009
    - Program no. 09-7-348, Christian love, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 69)
      October 9, 1955
      February 15, 2009
    - Program no. 09-8-349, Newborn babes, their food, 1 Peter 2:1-3, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 70)
      October 16, 1955
      February 22, 2009
    - Program no. 09-09-350, God's spiritual temple, 1 Peter 2:1-3, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 71)
      Oct. 23, 1955
      Mar. 1, 2009
    - Program no. 09-10-351, Be on your guard, 1 Peter 2:9-20, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 72)
      Oct. 30, 1955
      Mar. 8, 2009
    - Program no. 09-11-352, Footprints of Jesus, 1 Peter 2:21-25, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 73)
      Nov. 5, 1955
      Mar. 15, 2009
    - Program no. 09-12-353, The days of Noah, 1 Peter 3:1-18, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 74)
      Nov. 2, 1955
      Mar. 22, 2009
    - Program no. 09-13-354, The way home, 1 Peter 4:1-1, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 75)
      Nov. 27, 1955
      Mar. 29, 2009
    - Program no. 09-14-355, The way home, 1 Peter 4:8-19, 1 compact disc (Audio 1, Disc 76)
      Dec. 4, 1955
      Apr. 5, 2009
    - Program no. 09-16-357, The chief shepherd shall appear, 1 Peter 5:1-4, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 77)
      Dec. 11, 1955
      Apr. 19, 2009
    - Program no. 09-17-358, The god of all grace, 1 Peter 5:10, 1 compact disc (Audio 1, Disc 78)
      Apr. 26, 2009
      Dec. 18, 1955
    - Program no. 09-18-359, Peter's ministry, Acts 9:32-43, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 79)
      May 3, 2009
    - Program no. 09-15-356, The resurrection and the believers, 1 Cor. 15:35, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 80)
      Original broadcast number
      759
      Apr. 12, 2009
    - Program no. 09-19-360, The gospel to the gentiles, acts 10:1-23, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 81)
      May 10, 2009
    - Program no. 09-20-361, Jesus, judge or savior, Acts 10:23-48, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 82)
      May 17, 2009
    - Program no. 09-21-362, The perfect program for spreading the gospel, Acts 11:19-30, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 83)
      May 24, 2009
    - Program no. 09-22-363, Peter and Herod Agrippa, Acts 12, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 84)
      May 31, 2009
    - Program no. 09-24-364, The Church to Antioch, Acts 13:1-3, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 85)
      June 7, 2009
    - Program no. 09-24-365, Barnabas and Paul faced opposition, Acts 13:4-12, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 86)
      June 14, 2009
    - Program no. 09-26-366, Glad tidings, Acts 13:13-41, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 87)
      June 21, 2009
    - Program no. 09-26-367, Two kinds of response to the gospel, Acts 13:42-52, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 88)
      June 28, 2009
    - Program no. 09-28-368, Controversy in the early church, Acts 15, 1 compact disc (Audio 1, Disc 89)
      Jul. 5, 2009
    - Program no. 09-29-369, Paul at Jerusalem Council, Acts 15:14-18, 1 compact disc (Audio 1, Disc 90)
      Jul. 12, 2009
    - Program no. 09-30-370, Spiritual guidance, Act 15:36, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 91)
      Jul. 19. 2009
    - Program no. 09-31-371, Forbidden by the Holy Spirit to preach, Acts 16:6, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 92)
      Jul. 26, 2009
    - Program no. 09-32-372, Sailing a straight course, Acts 16:11, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 97)
      Orignal broadcast date
      Aug. 2, 2009
    - Program no. 09-32-373, Paul's 2nd missionary journey, Acts 16:18, 1 compact disc (Audio 1, Disc 98)
      Aug. 9, 2009
    - Program no. 09-34-374, Paul at Thessalonica, Acts 17:1-15, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 99)
      Aug. 16, 2009
    - Program no. 09-35-375, Paul at Berea, Acts 17:11-12, 1 compact disc (Audio 1, Disc 100)
      Aug. 23, 2009
    - Program no. 09-36-376, A threefold description of an apostrate, Jude 8-10, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 101)
      Aug. 30, 2009
    - Program no. 09-37-377, The blessed hope, 1 Thes. 4:13, 14, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 102)
      Sept. 6, 2009
    - Program no. 09-38-278, Apostasy in the last days, Jude 4, 1 compact disc (Audio 1, Disc 103)
      Sept. 13, 2009
    - Program no. 09-39-379, Those who depart from the faith, 1 Tim. 4:1-3, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 104)
      Sept. 20, 2009
    - Program no. 09-40-380, God's judgement of apostates, Jude 14, 15, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 105)
      Sept. 27, 2009
    - Program no. 09-41-381, Reception and responsibility of the gospel, 1 Th. 1:1-10, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 106)
      Oct. 4, 2009
    - Program no. 09-42-382, The character of Apostle Paul, 1 Th. 2:1-4, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 107)
      Oct. 11, 2009
    - Program no. 09-43-383, A model preacher, 1 Th. 4:13-14, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 108)
      Oct. 18, 2009
    - Program no. 09-44-384, Our responsibility in light of Christ's returen, 1 Th. 3:11-13, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 109)
      Oct. 25, 2009
    - Program no. 09-45-385, The return of Christ, 1 Th. 4:13-18, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 110)
      Nov. 1, 2009
    - Program no. 09-46-386, The last trumpet, 1 Th. 4:16-17, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 111)
      Nov. 8, 2009
    - Program no. 09-47-387, How to occupy in the light of his soon return, 1 Th. 5, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 112)
      Nov. 15, 2009
    - Program no. 09-48-388, The coming great apostasy, 2 Th. 2:1-12, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 113)
      Nov. 22, 2009
    - Program no. 09-49-389, Living water, John 4:10, 15, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 114)
      Nov. 29, 2009
    - Program no. 09-50-390, Will we know our loved ones in Heaven, Rev. 21, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 115)
      Dec. 6, 2009
    - Program no. 09-51-391, The light of the world, John 9:5, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 116)
      Dec. 13, 2009
    - Program no. 09-52-392, Charles E. Fuller and Christmas music, Lk 2:1-20, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 117)
      Dec. 20, 2009
    - Program no. 09-53-393, The new birth and growth of a soul, John 4:46-53, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 118)
      Dec. 27, 2009
    - Program no. 10-1-394, The great physician makes soul whole, John 5:1-9, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 119)
      Jan. 3, 2010
    - Program no. 10-2-395, The feeding of the five thousands, John 6:1-14, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 120)
      Jan. 10, 2010
    - Program no. 10-3-396, The Lord's sustenance and surplus, John 6:10-12, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 121)
      Jan. 17, 2010
    - Program no. 10-4-397, Jesus calms the sea, John 6:15-21, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 122)
      Jan. 24, 2010
    - Program no. 10-5-398, The bread of life, John 6:35, 36, 56, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 123)
      Jan. 31, 2010
    - Program no. 10-6-399, Him that thirsteth, John 7:37-39, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 124)
      Feb. 7, 2010
    - Program no. 10-7-400, The woman taken in adultery, John 8:1-11, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 125)
      Feb. 14, 2010
    - Program 10-8-401, The divine provision, Luke 5:1-11, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 126)
      Feb. 21, 2010
    - Program 10-9-402, The man born blind from birth, John 9, 1 CD-R (Audio 1, Disc 127)
      Feb. 28, 2010
- Gospel music recordings, 1999-2004; 2; 6 mixed media: 2 sound cassettes + 4 compact discs (Audio 1)
  - Cassette tape album no. 7, Old Fashioned Revival Hour Quartet, 1993; 1 audiocassette; Old Fashioned Revival Hour Quartet. (Audio 1, Cassette 1)
    In tenderness he sought me -- Nearer, still nearer -- Somebody's knocking at your door -- My heavenly home -- Jesus, rose of Sharon -- Seeking the lost -- There'll be no more tears in Paradise -- The way of the cross leads home -- Love found a way -- My Lord's gonna move this wicked race -- Deeper yet, deeper yet -- Living for Jesus -- More like the master, my heavenly Father watches over me -- Let Him have his way with thee -- Bring them in -- Saved, saved -- Sun of my soul -- Near to the heart of God -- The far away land -- Tell me the story of Jesus -- We'll meet each other there -- Glorious things of Thee are spoken -- Take the name of Jesus -- Heavenly sunshine -- His yoke is easy ,his burden is light -- What a friend.
  - Cassette tape album no. 8, Old Fashioned Revival Hour Quartet, 1995; 1 audiocassette; Old Fashioned Revival Hour Quartet. (Audio 1, Cassette 2)
    Brethern we have met to worship -- I'll be a friend to Jesus -- He lifted me -- On Jordan's strand -- We'll never say good-bye -- Hold Thou my hand -- To the work -- Jesus the very thought of thee -- Sound the battle cry -- Jesus I my cross have taken -- I'm happy in my savior, he's the one -- Tell me the old, old story -- The banner of the cross -- Victory through grace -- I am coming nearer -- I remember Calvary -- The home over there -- I shall know him -- Lord I want to be a Christian -- Come to the savior -- Jesus means everything to me -- Dare to stand like Joshua -- Majestic sweetness sits enthroned -- Meet me there -- When is see my savior -- Jesus is tenderly calling.
  - Tell me the old, old story, 1999; 1 compact disc; Brown, Dick, baritone; Old Fashioned Revival Hour Quartet. (Audio 1, Disc 92)
    Fire song -- Hold thou my hand -- Whispering hope -- Once to every man and nation -- Tell me the old, old song -- When I see my savior -- Let the lower lights be burning -- Thou remainist Christ my all -- What a friend we have in Jesus -- Near to the heart of God
  - Start your life anew, 2000; 1 compact disc; Old Fashioned Revival Hour Choir. (Audio 1, Disc 93)
    Start your life anew with Jesus: medley -- He put a song in my heart -- All that I need is Jesus -- Eternal Father, strong to save -- Fire song -- Anywhere with Jesus -- Precious Lord, take my hand -- Brighten the corner -- Tell me the story of Jesus -- He is so precious to me -- Shelter in the time of storm -- Dear Lord and Father of mankind -- Beyond the sunset -- Good night and good morning -- What if it where today.
  - How great Thou art, 2003; 1 compact disc; Old Fashioned Revival Hour Quartet. (Audio 1, Disc 94)
    How great Thou art -- Now I belong to Jesus -- Are you ready? -- I need Thee every hour -- When I see my savior -- I will arise and go to Jesus -- Redwoods -- There's glory in my soul -- My heavenly Father watches over me -- He is mine -- Will the circle be unbroken -- Look away to heaven -- Near to the heart of God -- I know my redeemer lives -- They are nailed to the cross -- We worship and adore Thee.
  - Rudy Atwood and the Ralph Carmichael String Quartet, 2004; 1 compact disc; Atwood, Rudy; Ralph Carmichael String Quartet. (Audio 1, Disc 95)
    Come thou font -- Yield not to temptation -- Jesus I my cross have taken -- Beneat the cross of Jesus -- Free as a bird -- Jesus I come -- Like a river glorious -- He the pearly gates will open -- God leads his dear children along -- O Jesus I have promised -- I gave my life for Thee -- My faith looks up to Thee -- Blessed assurance -- No not one -- Day by day -- Near the cross -- Precious hiding place -- No night there -- His eye is on the the sparrow -- Come ye disconsolate -- Jesus I am resting -- God will take care of you -- Nearer my God to thee -- Blessed quietness.